If we scroll through our DataFrame a bit more,
如果我们多滚动一下 DataFrame
we'll notice that Pandas automatically collapses some columns
我们会注意到 Pandas 自动折叠较大数据集的一些列和行
and rows of larger DataSets like this one, which you can see here.
比如这里
Between row 29 and row 18,971,
在第 29 行和第 18,971 行之间
all of the rows are collapsed using these ellipses here.
所有行都是使用省略号折叠的
And the same thing is true if we scroll right here and check out all of our columns.
如果我们向右滚动 并检查所有列 发现也是一样的
Every column between duration and salary was again collapsed using these ellipses.
duration (在职时间)和 salary (工资) 之间的各列也是使用这些省略号折叠
Pandas does this because viewing large DataSets takes up too much space.
Pandas 这样处理 是因为查看大数据集会占用太多空间
And scrolling that much can cause headaches.
滚动起来也会令人头疼
This is also the downside I mentioned previously,
这也是我之前谈到的缺点
about visual assessment being difficult in Pandas.
即在 Pandas 中难以进行目测评估
Uncollapsing these columns and rows is finicky,
展开这些列和行过于繁琐
and scrolling up and down and side to side in Jupyter Notebook cells isn't great.
在 Jupyter notebook 单元格中上下和横向滚动也非易事
Instead, I like to use Pandas's Info function to get more information about our DataSet.
相反 我喜欢用 Pandas 的INFO函数获得更多关于我们数据集的信息
This is a form of programmatic assessment.
这就是一种编程评估
This function is extremely simple.
这个函数极为简单
We type the name of our DataFrame,
我们键入 DataFrame 的名称
which is df, then .Info.
即 df 然后 .info
And again, I'll use SHIFT and TAB here,
这时候 我将会再次利用 SHIFT+TAB
to explore the Signature and Docstring of the function.
探索这个函数的 Signature 和 Docstring
Okay. Signature, DF dot info and Docstring.
好的 Signature、df.info 和 Docstring
Concise summary of a DataFrame.
DataFrame 的简明摘要
Docstring tells us what the function does.
Docstring 告诉我们这个函数的作用
Okay. So we'll process this cell, SHIFT and ENTER.
好的 我们将处理这个单元格 SHIFT+ENTER
And here's that Concise Summary.
这就是简明摘要
We've got 19,001 entries and 24 columns.
我们得到 19,001 行和 24 列
Then, a bunch of information about each of those columns below,
然后 一连串关于下方各列的信息
including the types of values in those columns
包括这些列的值的类型和
and the total memory usage of the DataFrame.
DataFrame 的总内存使用量
Okay. So let's look through these columns a bit.
好的 我们再仔细检查这些列
What is ApplicationP?
什么是 ApplicationP ？
What's AboutC?
什么是 AboutC？
One of the fundamentals of quality data is having descriptive variable and value names.
优质数据的基本要素之一是具有描述性变量和值名称
Even RequiredQual, which means required qualifications, isn't that descriptive.
即使表示必要资格的 RequiredQual 也不是描述性变量
Even JobRequirment, which has a small typo in it,
JobRequirment 有个小小的输入错误
that's descriptive enough, but you might as well fix it if we can.
虽然它的描述性足够了 但如果可以的话 你也可能需要修复它
Let's make a note to clarify all of these when cleaning.
我们做下记录 以便在清洁时处理所有问题